叫布鲁克怎样
How about the name Brook?
她看着一点不像是布鲁克
She just doesn't seem like Brook anymore
布鲁克·雷恩[发音同纽约市区]
Brook Lane
她是个小孩  不是个城市
She is a baby, not a city.
你怎么想  有什么好主意吗
What do you think about it? Got some new suggestions?
托埃德
Toddet
我饿了
I am hungry.
我给你们找点吃的来
I will get you guys something to eat.
你会没事的
You are OK.
好了
OK.
有人呼我
I was paged.
你来这里干什么
What are you doing here?
我们能去别处谈吗
Can we talk somewhere?
我在想  我们
I was thinking...to us
萨拉
Sarah
在
Yeah
宝宝哪里去了
Where is the baby?
没人看见任何人进出  婴儿不在育儿室
No one saw anyone go in or out, and the baby is not in the nursery
她是什么情况
What's her condition?
5周早产  剖腹产  因母亲体态笨重
5 weeks preterm, C-section because the mom is pretty clumsier.
看看父亲怎么说
Said the father
洛津斯基先生
Mr. Lozinski
我是丽莎·卡迪医生  院长
Dr. Lisa Cuddy, Dean of Medicine.
你离开病房多久
How long were you out of the room?
最多15到20分钟的样子
15 to 20 minutes, top.
附近有警报吗
Was there a proximity alarm?
你们孩子带着的手链内含芯片
The bracelet on your baby's ankle has a microchip
要是她带着它离开  会触发警报
that would set off alarm if she carries it through an exit.
通知警察  关闭所有出口
Call the police, shut down all the exit.
我们处于封闭状态
We are on lock down.
找到婴儿前  谁也不能离开
Nobody moves untill we find that baby.
你为什么要寄离婚协议呢
Why would you send the divorce papers?
是我计划列表上要做的  对不起
It's been on my to-do list. Sorry.
你已经签了吗
Well, you signed them?
等到我们能认真讨论过我们的婚姻后
Not until we have a real conversation about our marriage
我错了  我来了  抱歉
Hey, I made a mistake. I am here. I am sorry.
我要你看一下这个副本
I need you to read this copy here.
7号警报  7号警报
Code 7, code 7
请所有无关工作人员及访客留在所在区域
All non essential personnel and guest, please remain where you are.
保安人员请到待命区集合
Security personnel should report to their staging areas
等候指令
and wait for further instructions.
病人请留在病房
For patients, please remain in your rooms
若需要医疗帮助  请使用呼叫按钮
and use call buttons if you need medical assistance.
请保持冷静  等待医院工作人员到达
Please remain calm and wait for hospital personnel to come to you.
警报解除前  请不要试图离开你的房间
Do not try to leave your room until the code seven has been lifted.
-请清空过道  -护士  别管它
- Please clear hallways. - Nurse, just leave it.
别管了  你现在需要进病房
Leave it. You need to get into the room now.
一旦发现可疑情况
Please notify hospital personnel or police immediately
请立即通知医院工作人员或警察
if you see anything suspicious.
目前我们不能让任何人离开医院
We cannot allow anyone to leave the hospital at this time.
所有工作人员请在待命区域等候
All personnel should remain in their staging areas
除非有保安部门的指令
Unless otherwise instructed by security.
对  对  对  清空这里
Yeah, yeah, yeah, gotta clear the--
多谢耐心合作
Thank you for your patience and cooperation.
除了护士外  还有其他人
And did anyone other than your nurses
询问过你女儿吗
Ever come by asking about your daughter?
没  没有  就那两个
No. No, just those two.
-我马上登记  -等等
- I'll check in soon. - Wait.
-你在干什么  -不 我要帮他们找
- What are you doing? - No, I need to help them look.
你得待在床上
Ow! You have to stay in bed.
你扯到缝合处了
You pulled a stitch.
躺下  我来处理
Lay back down. I got it.
给你点药物帮助你放松  如何
Why don't I give you something to help you relax?
不  不要  我不想放松
No, no, I don't want to relax.
我想找到我的孩子
I want to find my baby.
警察正一个一个房间搜查
The police are searching room by room.
谁会带走她呢
Who would take her?
她要是饿了需要哺乳怎么办
What if she needs to be fed?
我们会找到她的
We're gonna find her.
警察为何不找我们的护士谈话呢
Why aren't the police talking to our nurse?
现在干什么呢
What now?
真心话大冒险吗
Truth or dare?
别  惹我可不好玩
Oh, no, you don't want to mess with me.
牛顿北高的真心话大冒险女王
True or dare queen at Newton North.
我开玩笑的
I was kidding.
我保证我们能找到些有趣的话题
I'm sure we can find something interesting
而不用靠那些幼稚的游戏
To talk about without relying on some juvenile game.
当然
Sure.
真相
Truth.
他们觉得我带走了孩子吗
They think I took the kid?
你觉得我会做这些...
Do you think I would do something--
不  我就是问问罢了
No, I'm just asking questions.
那天  我让那哥哥
The day I let the older brother
第一次抱了婴儿
Hold the baby for the first time--
我把她放在他腿上
So I put her in his lap.
过了几秒  她开始尖叫
After a few seconds, she shrieked.
我很肯定  他掐了她
I'm pretty sure he pinched her.
我需要知道这些事情
I need to know this stuff.
任何不正常的
Anything out of the ordinary.
小孩子间争风吃醋而已
It was sibling rivalry.
我以为没什么大不了
I thought it was kind of ordinary.
你来这里干什么
What are you doing down here?
我来找麦克纳的病例档案
I was looking for Mckenna's patient file.
你是指这个吗
Oh, you mean this file?
我说过我来取的这个吗
The one I said I'd get?
你都取了两个小时了
Two hours ago?
莫非你连取档案的责任心这种事
Seriously, you don't trust me
都不能信任我吗
with the immense responsibility of fetching a file?
既然你都找到了
If you already found it,
还在翻什么
what are you looking through those for?
你知道这些是什么吗
Do you know what these are?
员工信誉档案
The staff credentials files.
这些应该在人力资源部门才对
Those should all be in H.R.
放在这里做数字化归档
Down here to be digitized.
既然我们被锁在了这里
And we're locked in, and whoever's supposed
而应该看这些的人被锁在了外面
to be watching 'em is locked out.
我们可以看到所有人的隐私
We could look up anything on anyone.
不法纪录
Malpractice records,
重罪纪录 收起来
felony histories. Put them away.
别这样
Come on.
上帝给我们开了一个小窗
We have a tiny window of opportunity
让我们可以偷窥到同事的隐私
to gain some insight into our colleagues.
好吧  要不只偷窥老板行吗
Okay. What if we just snoop on the boss?
这个主意我还可以接受
I think I can live with that.
你现在每小时注射2毫克吗啡
You're on two milligrams of morphine an hour.
怎么可能还醒着
How the hell are you still awake?
等等  先别告诉我
No, don't tell me.
缺血性心肌病
Ischemic cardiomyopathy.
如果血液无法到达肠道
If the blood's not reaching your gut,
会引起肠灌注不足
you have intestinal hypoperfusion.
这强过麻醉剂的作用  使你清醒
That'd be stronger than the narcotics.
护士说我可能只剩一两天可以活了
The nurse said I might only have a day or two left.
她在安慰你呢
She was being kind.
你就是豪斯医生
You're Dr. House,
对吗
aren't you?
我的天  可别说我们曾经拍拖过
Oh, god, don't tell me we used to date.
拐棍  我看过关于你的报道
The limp. I read about you.
我给你写了一封信
I sent you a letter
那时他们还没找到病因
before they knew what was wrong.
我希望你能接下我的病例
I tried to get you to take my case.
是啊  你应该把报道看完的
Yeah, well, you should have kept reading.
心脏病这种小病请不起我的
Heart disease is kind of below my pay grade.
最开始只是牙疼
It started as tooth pain.
没有人想到会是心脏问题
No one got it that it was a heart problem.
直到后来一系列的心脏病发
Till I had a series of massive heart attack--
你不会觉得心烦吗
this doesn't bother you?
你是指你满嘴污秽吗
You talking with your mouth full?
-有一点  -我是指
- A little. - I meant the fact
你站在这里眼睁睁地看着我死
that you're standing here watching me die
就因为我的病例太平淡
because my file bored you.
我的录取比率是二十分之一
I take maybe 1 in 20 cases.
被我拒绝的人大多都死了
A lot of the people I turn down end up dying.
你要这么想
It's really a good argument
世界上不只我一个人能看病
for there being more than one me
这样你就感觉好多了
when you think about it.
-真心话  -好的
- Truth. - All right.
你玩过三P没
Have you ever had a threesome?
没有
No.
你没玩过吗
You haven't?
双性恋就一定要玩三P吗
Wait, just-- just because I'm bisexual?
当然
Well, yeah.
你懂双性恋是什么意思吗
Do you understand what bisexual means?
"双"可不是指同时和两个人做爱
It doesn't mean you have sex with two people at once.
顺便说一句  你没问我玩过四P没有
And by the way, you didn't ask me if I'd had a foursome.
真心话还是大冒险
Truth or dare?
等等  你玩过四P吗
Wait. You've had a foursome?
没有  但现在你问了我两个问题
No, but now you've asked me two questions,
所以我也要问你两个
so I get to ask you two.
这就是为什么我是女王
You see why I was the queen.
肯定不是沃克干的
Walker wouldn't do anything.
他也是我的儿子
He's my son too.
我也不想说的太残酷
I don't mean to sound cold,
但他毕竟只是养子
but he's your stepson.
我们要考虑所有的可能性
We can't ignore any possibility.
沃克最近在学校里
Walker's been getting in fights a lot
经常和人打架
at school lately.
上周  他用书打了另一个孩子
Last week, he hit another kid with a book
打出了血
hard enough to draw blood.
要是他对我的宝宝做了什么
If he did something to the baby...
我们当时正在努力解决
We were working on it.
却没有成功
And we failed.
不是  你和豪斯谈过以后
No, you had a conversation with house,
回到家  只是通知我
then came back, informed me
我已经被他毒害太深
I'd been forever poisoned by him,
然后就开始收拾行李
and started packing.
这么说可真有意思
It's interesting how your story leaves out the part
怎么不提你杀了一个人的那部分呢
where you murdered another human being.
一个想实施种族屠杀的独裁者
A dictator who was committing genocide.
你当时自己也想那么干来着
You thought about doing it yourself.
-但我没干  -对
- But I didn't. - Right.
因为你中他的毒没我深
Because you're not toxic like I am.
你以为咱俩在这儿会怎么样
What do you think is gonna happen here?
你打算说服我回到你身边吗
You're gonna logic me into coming back?
这儿记录了三十多次医疗事故
There must be over 30 malpractice settlements in here.
他连CT都没做就去脑活检
He did a brain biopsy without CT mapping,
导致病人因脑疝死亡
causing brain herniation and death.
看这个
Look at this one.
他拙劣的阴茎切除术
Patient lost four liters of blood
害病人失了四升血
from a botched penisectomy.
这个病人叫丽莎·卡迪
On a patient named Lisa Cuddy?
该死的  这些病人都叫丽莎·卡迪
Damn it. They're all named Lisa Cuddy.
他人都不在这  还捉弄我们
He's not even here, and he's screwing with us.
这有什么好玩的
Where's the joy in that?
你真想知道他想些什么吗
You really want to get into his head?
想  但我不打算刺伤自己的腿
Yeah, but I decided against stabbing myself in the leg
或是对止疼药上瘾
or getting addicted to pain pills.
你可以  跳过刺腿那步
You can, uh... skip the stabbing.
你从哪弄来的
Where did you--
从门诊一个骗药的人那没收的
Confiscated them from a drug seeker in that clinic.
还没来得及上交呢
Didn't get a chance to turn 'em in.
反正要在这待好几个小时
It is after hours.
我吃一片好了
I'll take one.
体会体会豪斯的处境
Walk in House's shoes for a night.
一片
One?
他可不只吃这么点儿
I believe he wears a larger size.
没有卡片  没有鲜花
No cards, no flowers,
连个电话都没有
Not even a phone call.
我猜猜  你是灯塔管理员
Let me guess. Lighthouse keeper.
我在普林斯顿当了26年的古典文学教授
I was a classics professor at princeton for 26 years.
主要是做研究
Mostly research.
也就是说你最亲近的同事两千年前就死了
So your closest colleagues died 2,000 years ago.
肯定是这样
That must be it.
不是说你没有朋友
Not that you have no friends
只是因为你是个可悲的混蛋
Because, say, you're a miserable bastard.
关你什么事
What do you care?
接下来几个小时会很难熬
The next few hours are gonna be grim.
等我尽快离开这里后
There'll be nausea, pain, no company,
你会觉得恶性  疼痛  没人陪你
As soon as I can get myself out of here.
我可以把阀门松开
I can unlock the regulator.
麻醉剂会让你失去知觉
You can put yourself in a narcotic haze,
就此安息
Sleep blissfully to the end.
这是在帮我还是帮你
Oh, is that a favor to me or to you?
双赢
Win-win.
不用了  谢谢
No, thanks.
你想让我因为没接收你这个病例而愧疚吗
Are you trying to guilt me for not taking your case?
你以为古典主义者不相信命运吗
You think a classicist doesn't believe in fate?
你觉得奥德修斯[特洛伊]会像个败者一般
You think Odysseus would lie whimpering
躺在病床上啜泣不止吗
like a loser in a hospital bed?
按我的建议做吧
Come on, take my offer.
沉浸在药物带来的快感之中  平静离世
Take the drug holiday. Numb yourself out.
我觉得你才是把自己封闭得沉默的人
I think you're the one who wants to numb himself out.
真心话
Truth.
你向你爸爸坦白双性恋时  他有什么反应
How did your dad react when you came out to him?
泡了杯茶给我
He made me tea.
真的  不管我告诉他什么
Seriously. Doesn't matter what I tell him.
他都笑着告诉我  他支持我
He smiles, tells me he supports me,
还泡薄荷茶给我喝
And makes me some peppermint tea.
真心话还是大冒险
Truth or dare?
真心话
Um, truth.
你在谈恋爱吗
Are you dating anyone?
现在吗  没有
Now? No.
有意思
Interesting.
你加了个修饰语
You added a modifier.
真心话
Truth.
你和福曼约会的时候
Um, when you were dating Foreman...
-不不不  -怎么啦
- No, no. No. - What?
如果是他或者我俩的私事
If it was something personal about him or us,
我觉得不太方便回答
I just don't think that's right to answer.
毕竟大家是同事
We all work together.
可这才是这个游戏的关键
That's the whole point of this game--
私人的  最好是窘事
Something personal, preferably embarrassing.
换点别的吧
Just pick something else.
这就是你的问题了
You see, this is your problem.
你装成一副很开明的样子
You act like you're so liberal and open,
其实你一点都不开明
But you are the least--
我变卦了  大冒险别让 我脱衣服就行
I changed my mind. Dare. Just no nudity.
就脱衣服吧
Yes, nudity.
我想让你把胸部
I want you to show your breasts
给陶博看
to Taub.
这是有史以来最蠢的大冒险了
That is the most idiotic dare ever.
你玩没玩过这个游戏啊
Have you ever played this game?
我觉得让你把胸部给我看
Well, I thought showing me your breasts
有点趁人之危
would be a little exploitative.
你说的大冒险是未来的  大天才
Your dare is in the future, genius.
嘿  你是说你会食言吗
Hey, if you're saying you won't do it...
不不  我当然会把我的胸部给陶博看
No, no, no, of course I'll show my breasts to Taub.
可能是明天
Tomorrow, perhaps,
或者明年的什么时候
or maybe some time next year, you know,
因为我要捍卫我的荣誉
because I'm honor-bound.
真心话还是大冒险
Truth or dare?
你现在不开心我能理解
It's understandable that you wouldn't be happy right now.
要面对生活的变数
Your world is changing.
害怕吗
You scared?
你对你妹妹怎么想
And how do you feel about your sister?
我讨厌她
I hate her.
沃克  这很重要
Walker, this is important.
你有没有把宝宝怎么样了呢
Did you do anything to the baby?
是不是把她抱去哪儿了
Did you move her somewhere?
-把她藏起来了  -没有
- Hide her? - No.
我们不会怪你的
Nobody'd be mad at you.
我说了没有  别再问我了
I said no, so stop asking me.
一天都疼得厉害
Bad pain day?
整个月都疼得厉害
Bad pain month.
自从我戒毒瘾以来
Since I'm not using it...
如果你不想要吗啡
Oh, if you don't want the morphine,
你一定自己藏着什么秘密武器吧
you must have something of your own, hmm?
我那时在戒毒
I was in rehab.
我的秘密武器出了点小小的问题
I had a little problem with the something of my own.
我现在只吃布洛芬[抗炎镇痛药]
Now all I take is ibuprofen,
结果疼痛加重了两级
And it's two flights up.
一整个月都这样吗
For the whole month?
疼痛感转移了
The pain's migrated.
我估计是动脉血管壁被破坏了
I think the arterial wall is damaged.
什么  你没确认一下
What, you don't know?
我还没照过动脉X光
I haven't had an arteriogram yet.
其实你是不想去照
And you don't want the test.
你生怕动脉血管壁完好无损
In case the arterial wall is fine.
因为这就意味着
which would mean that the pain
疼痛有其他的来源
is coming from something else.
她叫什么名字
What's her name?
有意思
Interesting...
你的思维从病痛一下跳到离殇
That you jump from physical pain to long-lost love.
你这是感情投射
You're projecting.
你的那个她叫什么名字
So what's her name?
现在什么时间了
What time is it?
时间于你有何意义
What does it matter to you?
现在还剩四小时
It's "T" Minus four hours.
八点二十
8:20.
告诉我她是谁
Now tell me who she is
她来看你或是打电话给你
And what are the pathetically long odds
的可能性还剩下可怜的几分
That she's gonna visit or call.
还有为什么这会是你不肯吃吗啡的理由
And why that's a reason not to take the morphine.
房间还在打转吗
Is the room still spinning?
我眼前的在转
Mine is.
看来我们不该吃这么多
Maybe we shouldn't have taken so many.
我试试看能不能站起来
I'm gonna try to stand up.
你小心了
You be careful.
喔耶  成功了
Oh, yeah. That's working.
我的脸没知觉了
I can't feel my face.
不是吧
No way.
是
Way.
打我
Hit me.
什么
What?
打我的脸
Hit me in the face.
真的打
Seriously?
你心里早就想这么干了吧
You know you've always wanted to.
-现在机会来了  -是个好主意
- Now's your chance. - That's a great idea.
我们成立个搏击俱乐部
We start a fight club.
或许我们可以...
Maybe we...
天啊
Oh, my god!
你  酷毙了
You-- that is so cool!
好吧
Okay.
我的手还有感觉哦
I can still feel my hand.
我只是没作好准备
I wasn't ready.
你原本打算怎么着
What were you gonna do?
收缩你的山羊胡子肌
Flex your goatee muscles?
等等
Wait a minute.
这些是你的信誉档案吗
This is your credentials file?
给我
Hey, give me that.
原来你是为这个而来
That's why you came down here.
而不是病人档案
Not for the patient file.
你小子...
You wanted...
你居然想...
这样吧  Robert
Okay, Robert.
你想问什么
I will answer
我都回答你
whatever questions you want.
但过后你必须要签了这些文件
But then you're gonna have to sign the papers.
你爱过我吗
Did you ever love me?
你怎么问得出来
How can you even ask that?
你第一次和我上床
The first time you slept with me
是因为你当时吸了冰毒
was because you were on crystal meth.
我嗑药是因为我情绪上来了
I was on the drugs because I was emotional.
是我的感情到了我才投入你的怀抱
It was the emotions that led to the sex,
-不是因为药劲儿  -你说谎
- Not the drugs. - Not true.
之后除了性你拒绝我们之间进一步发展
After that, you refused to let it go further than just sex.
因为我知道对你有感觉  但我并不想那样
Because I knew I was falling for you and I didn't want to.
这一点从来没变过
And that never changed.
你中断了我们的假期只为我给你买了戒指
You broke off our vacation Because I bought you a ring.
我当时太紧张了  我也不想的
I got cold feet. I'm not proud.
之后你差点取消了我们的婚礼
And then you almost called off our wedding
因为你不能停止去想
Because you couldn't give up the idea
有一个你去世丈夫的孩子
Of having your dead husband's baby.
不要  不要把他卷进来
Don't! Don't bring him up!
就算那之后  你也不能确定对我的感情
Because even then, you weren't sure about me.
可能如果你嫁给我的时候我要死了
Maybe if I was dying when you married me,
-一切会有一点不同  -这不公平
- It would have been a bit different. - That's not fair.
这不仅公平  而且就是事实
It's not only fair, it's exactly the point.
你遇见他的时候他要死了
He was dying when you met him,
你们结婚才一年他就去世了
And he was gone just a year into the marriage.
你和他的婚姻只是一次蜜月
So it was all a honeymoon with him.
而我做的永远比不上那些
And I could never match up to that.
-第一次现实让我无法  -不要说了
- The first time reality intruded-- - Stop this.
-跟我说实话  -什么实话
- Just tell me the truth.- About what?
-你爱过我吗  -我不知道
- Did you ever love me?- I don't know!
谢谢你终于告诉我
Thank you for finally telling me.
真心话
Truth
你说你现在没有女朋友
You said you weren't dating anyone now.
意思是你之前有女朋友
Does that you mean you recently were,
还是你很快会有女朋友
Or soon will be?
哦  看看现在是谁放不开
Oh. Look who's guarded now.
你完全不在意聊你的性生活
You had no problem talking about your sex life,
但是你的爱情
But your love life...
好吧  大冒险
Fine. Dare it is.
从今以后再也不能看裸体
No nudity now or in the future.
你好的太过分了  威尔森
You're too much of a nice boy, wilson.
让我们释放坏孩子威尔森出来一会儿
Let's let the bad boy out for a bit.
你现在去偷一美元
You have to go steal one dollar right now.
偷谁的
From who?
哦  不是吧
Oh, come on.
呃  在霍普金斯医院实习
Uh, interned at hopkins.
早知道了  有了有了
Old news. Here we go.
留校察看
Academic probation.
我拜托你别再读了
I am asking you to please stop reading.
我恐怕不能那么做
I'm afraid I can't do that.
伪造一次实验结果  大错啊
Faked a lab result. Very wrong!
你下来打算在这些资料被数字化之前
And you came down to destroy the record
毁掉记录
Before it gets digitized.
永久地毁掉  错上加错啊
Permanentized. Even wronger.
我
I...
我得打败在我周围所有那些优秀的  被宠坏的孩子
I needed to beat all those elite, spoiled kids around me,
我要表现得没有弱点
To show no weaknesses,
在每件事上超越他们
To win at everything.
我干嘛跟你说这些
Why'd I just tell you that?
我嗑药以后总是话太多
I always talk too much when I'm stoned.
我干嘛要说这个
Why'd I just tell you that?
太傻了  你的成绩很优秀
It was stupid. You had great grades.
一次实验结果不应该影响到你
One lab result shouldn't have mattered.
可是一开始我就不认为自己配得上
Except I didn't think I deserved to be
去顶级的医科大学读书
At a top med school in the first place.
又来了
Again.
伪造实验结果是一回事
Faking lab results is one thing.
可你要到这儿毁掉记录
But you needing to come down here to destroy the records
而且在事发12年以后
12 years after the fact...
这不关大学的事
This isn't about med school.
是你不认为自己属于这儿
You don't think you belong here.
这家医院
At the hospital.
陶  逗号  克里斯托弗·迈克尔医生
Dr. Taub, Comma, Christopher Michael.
总之现在到了
So this is what it comes down to
最后的时光了
In the final hours.
人们美化失去的爱人
Deifying some lost love.
祈祷她接电话然后和她重归于好
Hoping to get her on the phone and make everything perfect.
可悲
It's pathetic.
不管是你为了什么离开了她
Either you left her for a reason
还是她为了什么离开了你
Or she left you for a reason.
-一个电话不会...  -是我的女儿
- A phone call is not... - It's my daughter.
那么为什么她不在这儿
So why isn't she here?
我离开了我的家人
I left my family...
而且是在格雷西六岁的时候
When Gracie was six.
实际上  是在我和一个学生发生了关系之后
I was sort of forced out, actually,
我就被驱逐了家门
After I'd had an affair with a student.
为了性还是爱呢
For sex or love?
都不是
Neither.
我会和格雷西的母亲结婚只是因为孩子
I'd only married Gracie's mother because of the baby.
但我觉得我无法承担誓约
But I didn't think I could handle commitment,
然后  和其它学术理论一样 我证明了自己是对的
And, like any decent academic, I proved myself right.
那你在乎现在几点是因为
And what time it is matters because?
她在亚特兰大做个舞蹈老师
She's a dance teacher in Atlanta.
她下班后九点回家
She gets home from work at 9:00,
我只想再和她说一次话
And I just wanted to speak to her one more time.
你的呢
What's yours?
挺像的  差不多
Same thing. Pretty much.
我几小时后就要死了
I'm gonna be dead in a few hours.
我不会泄露你的秘密的
Your secrets couldn't be safer.
除非你自己说出去
Unless you're keeping them from yourself.
我喜欢孤独
I like being alone.
至少我自认为这样最好
At least I convince myself that I'm better off that way.
直到我在一个精神病院
And then I met someone
遇到一个人
At a psychiatric hospital, of all places.
她改变了我
She changed me.
但她还是走了
And then she left.
我们还是孤独着好
We're better off alone.
独自痛苦着  孤身地死去
We suffer alone, we die alone.
不要在意你是否能当选
Doesn't matter if you're a model husband
年度模范丈夫或模范爸爸
Or father of the year.
明天对你来讲还是一样的
Tomorrow will be the same for you.
但昨天可能会有着不同的一面
But yesterday would have been different.
你好  达  达莉娅
Hey, dar--daria.
威尔森医生
Dr. Wilson.
你能帮我做个鸡肉三明治吗
Could you cook me up a chicken sandwich?
烤箱已经关了
Grill's closed.
是治病急需的
It's important medically.
哈德利医生正急需一份高蛋白肉食
Dr. Hadley needs a high-protein meal right now.
她不想谈起自己有这病
She doesn't like to talk about it,
但她有低蛋白血症
But she has hypoproteinemia.
我们有鸡肉沙拉
We got chicken salad.
是吗  但沙拉是凉的
Yeah. That's cold.
这种病必须要吃热蛋白质吗
She needs to eat warm protein for this disease?
我们可以给她吃凉蛋白质
Well, we could give her cold protein
只是其中的蛋白酶没有被激活
Whose uptake enzymes haven't been activated,
当然只要你不介意引起她肝脏和肾脏衰竭
As long as you don't mind her risking liver and kidney failure
最终导致死亡
And eventual death.
但  挺值得的
But, hey, it's worth it
这样你就不必再开烤箱了
So you don't have to flip on the grill.
你不必对此不爽
You don't have to be obnoxious about it.
你怎么看起来一点事都没有
How do you look so okay?
我已经花好几个月思考
I spent months wondering
我做错了什么以致如此
How I made it go bad.
如果你从没爱过我  那么...
If you never loved me, then--
那么就不是我的错了
Then I didn't do anything wrong.
艾莉森
Allison, come on.
没关系的
It's all right.
我也不知道我为什么那样说
I still don't know why I said that.
不是真的
It's not even true.
我真的爱你
I did love you.
只是...
Just...
可能方式决定了不会有结果
Not in a way that would have ever worked.
为什么不对
Why not?
因为你说的都是实话
Because everything you said is true.
我是个烂人
I'm a mess.
我嫁给了一个快要死去的男人
I married a man I knew was dying.
只有上帝知道我多么糟糕
So god knows how screwed up I already was.
他的死亡让我更混乱
Him dying messed me up even more.
我把你推出了我的生活
I pushed you out of my life.
是我太不确定
And I-I'm unfixable.
不是你
Not you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我也对不起你
I'm sorry too.
真心话
Truth.
闭嘴
Shut up.
对不起
I'm sorry.
不是你的错
It's not your fault.
不  是我不公平
No, I didn't even play fair.
你问我  当我告诉父亲
You asked me how my dad reacted
我是双性恋时他有什么反应
When I told him I was bisexual.
还有亨廷顿病
And the huntington's.
-没有吗  -我没告诉他
- No tea party? - I never told him.
他已经经历过够多的磨难了
He's been through enough.
所以他来看的是个异性恋健康的女儿
So he just visits his heterosexual, healthy daughter,
然后你们一起出去吃饭  看电影
And you go out to dinner and a movie
-谈论你家的花园  -我很晚才下班
- And talk about your garden? - I work late.
他住在我家里
He's staying at my house.
其实我尽量不回家
It's easier if I stay elsewhere
倒方便些
As much as I can.
你不能因为他的感觉影响自己的生活
You can't suppress your life for his convenience.
你不觉得有点讽刺吗
You don't see a little irony in that?
你就是为豪斯这么做的
That's exactly what you do for house.
他搬去和你一起住
When he moved in with you,
你为他买了一处更大的房子
You bought a bigger place for him.
怪不得你不去约会
No wonder you're not dating anyone.
没错
You're right.
那个女人  那个没和我在一起的女人
That woman, the woman I'm not involved with,
她叫萨姆·卡尔
Her name is sam carr.
但在1990到1991年间  她叫萨姆·威尔森
But in 1990 and 1991, it was sam wilson.
你前妻吗
Your ex-wife?
不  是我妈妈
No, my mother.
没错  就是我的前妻  首席前妻
Yes, my ex-wife. Ex number one.
几个星期前  她突然对我友好起来
She friended me a few weeks ago.
我们开始互发电邮
We started emailing.
原来她最近离婚了
It turns out she's recently divorced,
我想约她出来
And I wanted to ask her out.
你不能带女人出去吃饭
You can't take a woman to dinner,
不然的话豪斯又要
Or else house will go running
变得疯疯癫癫了
Straight back to the loony bin?
你根本不是在担心豪斯  而是在担心自己
You're not worried about house. You're worried about yourself.
因为她是你的前妻
Because she's an ex.
所以即便是吃顿饭也可能立刻就当真起来
So even dinner will mean it's immediately serious.
你还记得你当时最喜欢做的事吗
What are your favorite parts that you remember?
我最喜欢的就是半夜醒来
I liked how I would wake up in the middle of the night,
会发现你在睡梦中都会紧紧抱着我
You'd put your arm around me, and you wouldn't even wake up.
我还喜欢当你爸在圣诞节
I liked watching you stand up to your dad at christmas
对你妈大吼时  你站出来为你妈撑腰
When he yelled at your mom.
你都没意识到自己有多坚强
How you didn't even know you were strong.
但你真的很坚强
But you were.
你怀念什么
What do you miss?
我怀念很多东西
I miss a lot.
但每当我开始想念你时
But when I think about missing you,
我就会想到我们为婚礼
I think about that dance class
去参加的舞蹈班
That we took for the wedding.
很奇怪
It's weird.
我会想  他再也不会这样握着我的手了
I think, he's never gonna hold me like that again.
哦  天哪
Oh, god.
这一刻我会永远怀念的
I'm gonna miss this too.
你26岁就在新英格兰学刊上发表了文章
Published in the new england journal  at 26?
提前一年完成了实验室任务
Finished all the lab work a year earlier.
还带着一批医生
Led a group of surgeons
到孟加拉国去治疗裂唇
To fix cleft palates in bangladesh?
我能说什么呢  那台慈善晚会太感人了
What can I say? That concert was very moving to me.
-我不得不折服  -我不明白
- I have to take a knee. - I don't get it.
这应该是这里最优秀的档案了
This has got to be the most spectacular file down here.
为什么你还装出很羞愧的样子
Why are you pretending to be ashamed?
要是可以的话我会马上把你的档案换过来
I would trade mine for yours in a second.
当我在医学院的时候
When I was in med school,
我以为某天我像豪斯医生一样
I thought I'd be house some day.
可实际上
Instead, I am
我只能与这样的人共同工作
A fellow working with--
为比我年轻好几年的人工作
Working for people years younger than me.
所以我们都有后悔的事
So we both have a few regrets.
你应该为自己感到自豪
You should be proud of yours.
你的生活走的是上坡路
Your life's been trending up.
还是没有消息
No news.
你还支持得住吗
How you holding up?
你让他们给你打了针镇静剂
You let them sedate you?
没错
Yeah.
你有孩子么
Do you have kids?
一个小女孩
A little girl.
我去年领养了她
I adopted her last year.
我和唐纳德结婚后就领养了沃克
I adopted walker right after donald and I got married.
如果我不能像爱我女儿一样
What if I can never love walker
爱沃克的话呢
the way I love my daughter?
这会让我变成一个可憎的人吗
Does that make me a horrible person?
我去帮你拿点纸巾
Let me get you some tissues.
你叫人拿来了额外的浴巾吗
Did you request some extra towels?
没有
No.
什么  为什么这么问
What--why?
在萨拉的房间里有八条浴巾
There are eight towels in sarah's room.
哦
Okay.
应该只有四条的
There should only be four.
内勤部管理浴巾
Housekeeping handles towels.
帮我把他们的值班记录找出来
I need you to track down their logs,
查一下谁去过她房间  什么时候去的
Figure out who was up there and when.
就因为他们多给了浴巾
Because they got extra towels?
把记录找出来就是了  现在就去
Just find the logs. Now.
-阿德里安娜  你还好吗  -当然
- Adrienne, You okay? - Sure.
她怎么了
What's wrong?
阿德里安娜  把你的手臂伸出来
Adrienne, give me your arm.
她左臂上的汗毛竖起来了
The hair on her left arm is standing up.
非对称神经性功能失调
Asymmetric neurological function.
她动毛神经癫痫正在发作
She's having a pilomotor seizure.
可她一分钟前还好好的
She seemed fine a minute ago.
她刚才是没事
She was.
可能这一整天她都
She's probably been having
在经历复杂性癫痫
Complex seizures all day.
她基本像正常人一样活动
She would be basically functional,
可是却是不受控制的活动
But more or less acting on autopilot.
她可能到房间放了两次浴巾
She probably dropped the towels off twice.
有可能是她带走了孩子
She could have taken the baby.
我们一直都没有好好说声再见
We never really did have a proper good-bye.
已经9点了
It's 9:00.
我是格雷西  现在没法接电话
It's Gracie. I can't come to the phone,
请你留言
so please leave a message.
我猜她晚点了
I guess she's running late.
你看上去不太惊讶
You don't seem that surprised.
好像这是在意料之中
that's what you expected to get.
你故意等到她出门
You waited until you knew she'd be out.
她姑姑说她很晚才上班
Her aunt said that she starts work late.
我就时时趁此打电话
Every now and then,
听听她留下的声音
I just call to hear her voice on the machine.
她需要我时  我从未出现
I was never there when she needed me, so...
如今我又有什么资格求她前来
What right do I have to need her now?
当然没有
None.
我是说  你这个伪君子
Just means you're a hypocrite.
显然你有此资格
'cause apparently you do.
别管有没有资格这事了
Forget about rights.
把你该说的话告诉她
Just tell her what you need to tell her.
我是格雷西
It's Gracie.
我现在没法接电话
I can't come to the phone,
请你留言
so please leave a message.
格雷西
Gracie...
我是
This is...
爸爸
your father.
我爱你
I love you.
怎么样
Anything?
已经搜过了马尔多纳多记录上的所有房间
We've covered every room on Maldonado's logs.
查过了所有她去过的地方
been everywhere she's been.
另一辆车呢
Where's the other cart?
一般这里不是还有一辆车的吗
Isn't there usually another cart in here?
好了
Okay.
没事了
有人吗
Anyone in there?
一级防禁解除了
Lockdown's over.
我该走了
I should go.
是的
Yeah.
我刚刚约了山姆去吃晚饭
I just asked Sam to dinner.
小孩子总算成熟了啊
Little baby's all growed up.
你要告诉你爸吗
You gonna tell your dad?
我会去宾馆和他谈谈的
I'll stop by his hotel, talk to him.
宾馆吗
Hotel?
你明明说他住在你公寓的
You said he was staying at your apartment.
你刚才说过真话吗
Was there any truth in anything you said?
关于打电话给山姆是个好主意
The part about it being a good idea for you to call Sam.
那句是真的
That was true.
-晚安  雷米  -晚安  詹姆斯
- Good night, Remy.  - Good night, james.
警报已解除 重复  警报已解除
Code seven has been lifted. Repeat, code seven has been lifted.
要拿你的档案吗
You want your file?
不
Nah.
为你感到高兴
Good for you.
全体医院员工请离开集结地
All hospital personnel may leave their staging areas
向所属部门汇报
And report back to their departments.
多谢合作
Thank you for your cooperation.
不必向任何人说我们曾在这--
We don't have to tell anybody what we--
嗯
Mm-mm.
你拿到病人档案了吗
You got the patient file?
我就去拿  谢了
I'll grab it. Thanks.
明天见
See you tomorrow.
我想我准备好接受你的建议了
I think I'm ready to take you up on your offer.
豪斯医生
Dr. House?
防禁在几分钟前就解除了
Lockdown ended a few minutes ago.
嗯  我知道
Yeah. I know.
很遗憾没有接下你的案例
I'm sorry I didn't take your case.
我也是
Me too.
格雷西
Gracie...
会是你见过最可爱的6岁孩子
was the cutest six-year-old you ever saw.
今晚挺有趣吧
Interesting night, huh?
有意思
Interesting.